[♪♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa Pig.
[SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig has made
a special box for Peppa.
[SNORTS]
Peppa, this box
is just for you.
Thank you,
Mommy.
MOMMY PIG:
It's a secret box for you
to keep secret things in.
[SNORTS]
What things can I put in it,
Mommy?
Ho, ho. Only you
can decide that, Peppa.
It's your secret box.
[SNORTS]
I know what I can
put in it!
Good. But don't tell me.
[SNORTS]
I won't tell you,
or George or Daddy.
It's a secret.
[♪♪♪]
George, this is
my secret box.
[SNORTS]
It's empty.
I have to find some things
to put inside.
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George wants to help Peppa.
[SNORTS]
No, George, only I must know
what's in the box.
You have to wait outside
while I choose.
[SNORTS]
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
Peppa is going to choose
some secret things
to put in the box.
[PEPPA CONTINUES GIGGLING]
[SNORTS]
Now my secret box
is full.
[RATTLES]
George, you must not
look inside.
NARRATOR:
George would like to know what
is inside Peppa's secret box.
If you like,
you can try to guess.
[SNORTS]
[RATTLES]
Dine-Saw!
NARRATOR:
George thinks Peppa has put
a dinosaur in the box.
Oh, George! You always say
dinosaur for everything.
[SNORTS]
Anyway, a dinosaur is too big
to fit in the box.
NARRATOR:
George cannot guess what
is in Peppa's secret box.
Daddy Pig
is cleaning a picture.
Daddy!
This is my secret box.
Mommy made it for me.
[SNORTS]
It's very nice, Peppa.
What's inside?
It's a secret.
[SNORTS]
George tried to guess,
but he didn't get it right.
Can I have a try?
[SNORTS]
Yes!
[♪♪♪]
[RATTLES]
Hm. Have you put
my glasses inside?
No! Hee, hee! Your glasses
are on your head!
So they are!
[SNORTS]
Silly Daddy!
You must have
a proper guess.
Okay.
[SNORTS]
Have you put Mommy's shoes
in the box?
Nope. And that's
all your guesses, used up.
NARRATOR:
Peppa likes secrets.
[♪♪♪]
Mommy!
[SNORTS]
No one knows
what is in my box.
[RATTLES]
[SNORTS]
Oh.
What has George got?
[SNORTS]
I made a box
for George too.
And he's filled it
with secret things.
And only George knows
what's inside.
[RATTLES]
Oh.
NARRATOR:
Peppa would like to know
what is inside George's box.
[SNORTS]
It's George's toy dinosaur,
of course.
No!
NARRATOR:
George's toy dinosaur
is not in George's box.
Hee-hee-hee!
It's too difficult!
[SNORTS]
I'll never guess.
NARRATOR:
Peppa does not like secrets
as much as she used to.
Maybe, if you showed George
one thing from your box,
then he could show you
one thing from his.
Okay.
[SNORTS]
But we must do it
at the same time.
That's a good idea.
On the count of three, you each
show what's in your boxes.
Ready?
Yes.
One... two...
three.
NARRATOR: George has a drum...
[CHUCKLES]
...and Peppa has a trumpet.
[GIGGLES]
[PLAYING INSTRUMENTS]
Ho, ho! Lovely!
Yes, it sounds very nice.
Do you have any more
secret things?
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
NARRATOR
George has
a custard doughnut.
Oh.
NARRATOR
But Peppa's box is empty.
I've got nothing else.
Luckily, I have.
Come on, tuck in.
NARRATOR:
George, Peppa, Mommy Pig
and Daddy Pig
all like custard doughnuts.
I don't have a special box.
But I know a very good place
to hide my custard doughnut.
Can you guess where?
Hm...
Are you going to hide it
in the fridge?
No.
[SNORTS]
Somewhere much more special.
My tummy.
[MUNCHES]
Mm! Delicious!
[GIGGLES]
I'm going to hide mine
in my tummy.
Me too.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGHING AND SNORTING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
It is a bright, sunny day.
Peppa and her family
are in the park.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
They are going to fly a kite.
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
George is going to fly
the kite first.
[SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George runs as fast as he can.
But the kite won't fly.
[PANTING]
George, you're
doing it all wrong!
[SNORTS]
You didn't run fast enough.
Now it's my turn.
NARRATOR:
Peppa runs as fast as she can.
[GIGGLING]
NARRATOR:
But the kite still won't fly.
[PANTING]
[SNORTS]
The kite won't fly
if there isn't any wind,
no matter how fast
you run.
Oh.
[SNORTS]
We just have to wait,
until the wind
picks up a bit.
Oh.
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
Look!
It's getting windy.
NARRATOR:
Now that it is windy,
the kite can fly.
[LAUGHING]
[SNORTS, LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
The wind is quite strong now.
The wind is very strong now.
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
George!
Ha-ha-ha!
[CRIES]
Peppa!
Thank you, Daddy.
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Daddy Pig flies the kite.
Hooray!
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
Higher! Higher!
[♪♪♪]
[LAUGHING]
[DADDY PIG SNORTING
AND LAUGHING]
NARRATOR
Daddy pig flies the kite
very well.
Wow!
DADDY
Yes I am a bit of an expert
at these things.
[♪♪♪]
Watch out
for the trees!
You might get the kite
stuck in one.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
NARRATOR
Oh, dear. Daddy Pig has got
the kite caught in a tree.
Oh, no.
[SNORTS]
Hm.
Oh.
[CRYING]
MOMMY PIG:
Don't worry George.
Daddy will get the kite down.
Hooray!
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]
Uh, yes.
[GIGGLES]
Careful! There's
a big muddy puddle.
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love to jump
in muddy puddles.
Can we jump
in the puddle?
Please?
No. I don't want you
covered in mud.
Oh...
Stand back, children.
Please be careful, Daddy pig.
[SNORTS]
I know what I'm doing.
[♪♪♪]
[BRANCH CREAKS]
Please be careful.
[KIDS LAUGHING]
Just a bit further,
Daddy! Ha, ha!
Daddy Pig, you are much
too heavy for that branch.
[BRANCH CREAKS]
[SNORTS]
Nonsense.
I know exactly
how heavy I am.
[SNORTS]
There.
Hooray!
NARRATOR
Daddy Pig has rescued
the kite.
Whoa!
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear. Everyone is
covered in mud.
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
It's only mud.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Luckily, Daddy Pig
hasn't hurt himself.
And the kite
is out of the tree.
[IN UNISON]
Hooray! Ha-ha-ha!
[SNORTS]
Mommy, now that
we're all muddy,
can we jump
in the puddle?
[SNORTS]
I suppose so. After all,
you can't get any muddier.
[LAUGHING, SNORTS]
And I think Daddy Pig is going
to be doing the washing.
Oh...
[SNORTS]
[PEPPA & GEORGE LAUGHING,
SNORTS]
[♪♪♪]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George love jumping
up and down in muddy puddles.
Mommy and Daddy love jumping
Everyone loves jumping
up and down in muddy puddles.
[ALL LAUGHING AND SNORTING]
Jumping up and down
in muddy puddles
is just as much fun
as flying the kite.
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[LAUGHING]
NARRATOR
It is a lovely
bright, sunny day.
Peppa and her family
are going for a picnic.
Daddy Pig is bringing
the picnic basket.
[SNORTS]
Picnic blanket, bread, cheese,
tomatoes and lemonade.
Is there anything
we've forgotten?
[SNORTS]
Mommy's strawberry cake!
Ho, ho,
I was just teasing.
Mommy's homemade
strawberry cake is there too.
Is everybody ready?
Ready!
[IGNITION STARTING]
Then let's go!
[HORN HONKS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA SNORTS]
This looks like just the spot
for our picnic.
PEPPA, GEORGE, MOMMY PIG:
Hooray! Ha-ha-ha!
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
Ah! It's great
to be outdoors.
We should run around a bit
and get some exercise.
[SNORTS]
I want to eat,
then have a nap.
I certainly don't want
to run around.
Maybe Daddy should run
around a bit.
His tummy is quite big.
My tummy is not big.
[SNORTS]
But later, I will get
some exercise,
even if no one else does.
[LAUGHING]
Let's eat.
Good idea, Mommy Pig.
I'm really hungry.
[SNORTS]
[ALL MUNCHING]
Mm, delicious!
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[LAUGHS]
Ahh! I feel quite sleepy.
I thought you wanted to run
around a bit, Daddy Pig?
Later...
[SNORING]
[♪♪♪]
[SNORTS]
Look! There's a little
duck pond.
[QUACKS]
[SNORTS]
Mommy, can we feed
the ducks?
Yes, you can feed them
the rest of the bread.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
NARRATOR
Peppa and George love
feeding bread to ducks.
[QUACKING]
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
Mommy, I think
they want some more.
That was the last of the bread.
I'm sure
they've had enough.
[SNORTS]
Sorry, Mrs. Duck,
we've no more bread.
[QUACKING]
NARRATOR
The ducks want more food.
[SNORING]
So much for Daddy Pig
and his exercise.
[LAUGHING]
Uh, uh? What?
[QUACKING]
You lot again.
[SNORTS]
Peppa told you,
there's no more bread.
[QUACKS]
PEPPA: Mommy,
we do have
strawberry cake.
Well, if there's any cake
left over,
you can give it to the ducks.
[ALL LAUGHING]
NARRATOR:
Everyone likes Mommy Pig's
homemade strawberry cake.
[BUZZING]
Ooh! A wasp!
I hate wasps. Shoo!
What a fuss, Mommy Pig.
It's only a little wasp.
[CONTINUES BUZZING]
[GASPS] Go away, wasp!
Just stay still, Mommy Pig.
Then it will fly away.
[SNORTS]
There! You see,
all you had to was stay still.
Eh! Get away!
Scram! Whoa!
[SNORTS]
Help! Whoa! Shoo!
Get it off me! Whoa!
[SNORTS]
I hope the wasp
doesn't sting Daddy.
Whoa! Get away, you little pest!
[SNORTS]
No, Daddy Pig is running too
fast for the wasp to catch him.
Whoa!
[SNORTS]
Let's eat our cake before
the wasp comes back.
[ALL MUNCHING]
[♪♪♪]
[DUCK QUACKS]
Oh, no! We forgot to leave
any for the ducks.
[PANTING]
I think I lost it.
[SNORTS]
You said you would
run around
and get some exercise,
Daddy Pig.
But I didn't believe
you'd do it.
[KIDS LAUGH]
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
Luckily, I managed to hang on
to my slice of strawberry cake.
PEPPA:
Stop, Daddy!
We promised the rest
of the cake for the ducks.
Oh...
You are very lucky ducks.
[QUACKING, MUNCHING]
Say thank you to
Daddy Pig.
[QUACKS]
You're most welcome,
ho, ho!
It's time to go home.
Say goodbye to the ducks.
Bye, bye, ducks.
[QUACKING]
[SNORTS]
See you next time! Hee-hee!
[ALL LAUGHING, SNORTING]
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[QUACKING]
[♪♪♪]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig
have been tidying the house.
[RATTLES]
[SNORTS]
Mommy Pig and I found
this old box in the attic.
[BLOWS]
Ooh!
Can anyone guess
what's inside?
Hm, nope.
[SNORTS]
It's full of
musical instruments.
[ACCORDION PLAYS NOTE]
[IN UNISON]
Wow!
[DADDY PIG LAUGHS, SNORTS]
They are a bit old and dusty.
[BLOWS]
[SNEEZES]
[ALL LAUGH]
[SNORTS]
This is the violin I used
to play when I was little.
Mommy?
Can you play your violin?
I haven't played it
for a long time.
Please, Mommy!
Please play it!
[SNORTS]
I hope
I haven't forgotten how.
[PLAYING SLOW TUNE]
Bravo!
[ALL CLAPPING]
Hooray! Hee-hee!
[SNORTS]
Mommy?
Can I play the violin?
Hold it like this.
Yes, Mommy.
[PLAYS SCREECHY TUNE]
Oh!
NARRATOR:
Oh, dear.
I do not think it
is meant to sound like that.
[SNORTS]
George wants to try.
Hold it like this, George.
[SNORTS]
[PLAYING SCREECHY NOTES]
Oh!
NARRATOR:
That does not sound right
either.
The violin
is too hard to play.
Peppa...
[SNORTS]
...maybe you would do better
with this tin drum.
[SNORTS]
Thank you, Daddy.
[PLAYING DRUM]
NARRATOR: That sounds better.
Peppa loves
playing the drum.
Ho, ho! Lovely.
Yes, it sounds very nice.
[CONTINUES PLAYING DRUM]
This is Daddy Pig's
old accordion.
I used to play this to Mommy Pig
when we first met.
[PLAYS ROMANTIC MELODY]
Oh, Daddy Pig.
I remember this tune.
[PLAYS DRUM, LAUGHS]
[SNORTS]
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHS, SNORTS]
NARRATOR:
George wants to play
the accordion too.
Are you sure, George?
[SNORTS]
The accordion
is quite difficult.
George ,the a-cro-dion
is almost as difficult
to play as my drum.
[THWACK]
[SNORTS]
Okay, George.
[GIGGLING]
[PLAYING OFF-KEY TUNE]
Oh.
NARRATOR
Maybe George is a bit too
little to play the accordion.
Daddy?
[SNORTS]
What other instruments
are in the box?
Just this horn.
[SNORTS]
Can I try?
You have to blow it
very hard.
[INHALES]
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
NARRATOR
That does not sound right.
[SNORTS]
It's impossible!
I think I used to be able
to play it.
[INHALES]
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
NARRATOR:
That really does not sound
right.
[LAUGHING]
Maybe it just needs someone
big and strong like me.
[INHALES]
[BLOWING RASPBERRY]
NARRATOR:
That does not sound right
either.
[PANTS]
Peppa's right,
it is impossible to play.
Never mind, Daddy Pig.
Just stick to the accordion.
[SNORTS]
You play it beautifully.
Ho, ho! Well, I do
play it quite nicely,
even if I say so myself.
And I'll play my violin.
And I will play my drum.
NARRATOR:
Mommy Pig plays the violin.
[PLAYING SLOW TUNE]
Daddy Pig
plays the accordion.
[PLAYING ROMANTIC TUNE]
Peppa plays the drum.
[PLAYING SIMPLE TUNE]
But what instrument
will George play?
[PIGS CONTINUE PLAYING MUSIC]
[HORN BLASTS]
[LAUGHING]
George is blowing the horn!
Mommy couldn't play the horn
and Daddy couldn't play it.
And even I couldn't play it.
[SNORTS]
But George can play it!
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
[HORN BLASTS]
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[PIGS PLAYING
MUSICAL INSTRUMENTS]
[HORN BLASTS]
[LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLES, SNORTS]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]
[SNORTS]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTS, LAUGHS]
[SNORTS, GIGGLES]